<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Muse</title><link>https://RDLigeralde.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/</link><description>Recent content on Muse</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Roberto Ligeralde</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 23:01:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://RDLigeralde.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>USER STORIES</title><link>https://RDLigeralde.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/user_stories/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 13:22:53 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://RDLigeralde.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/user_stories/</guid><description>As a songwriter, I can easily search up the melodies I write so that I can make sure my compositions are original. As a music teacher, I can have my students practice writing their favorite songs in sheet music form so that they get comfortable with musical notation.
As an avid but untrained music listener, I can look up melodies stuck in my head so that I can get rid of pesky earworms.</description></item><item><title>State of the Community 02/2024</title><link>https://RDLigeralde.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/post/bootstrap-5-2-0-beta/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2022 13:00:44 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://RDLigeralde.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/post/bootstrap-5-2-0-beta/</guid><description>A thank-you to all our amazing musical contributors as we head into the Spring season! Last month, we broke our all-time record for user contributions, with over 3,000 new albums, EPs, and singles documented on Muse.
Congratulations to the winners of the January Top Contributer award: SkiiBaller and LongNamesAreWack, who will be receiving six months of Muse Pro free of charge.
UPDATE 03/19/24: Stay tuned for news on next round of the contribution context ;)</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://RDLigeralde.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://RDLigeralde.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/about/</guid><description>About Us Made with ❤️ by the Hugo Bootstrap Theme team.</description></item><item><title>Code of Conduct</title><link>https://RDLigeralde.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/code-of-conduct/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://RDLigeralde.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/code-of-conduct/</guid><description>Contributor Covenant Code of Conduct Our Pledge We as members, contributors, and leaders pledge to make participation in our community a harassment-free experience for everyone, regardless of age, body size, visible or invisible disability, ethnicity, sex characteristics, gender identity and expression, level of experience, education, socio-economic status, nationality, personal appearance, race, caste, color, religion, or sexual identity and orientation.
We pledge to act and interact in ways that contribute to an open, welcoming, diverse, inclusive, and healthy community.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://RDLigeralde.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://RDLigeralde.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/contact/</guid><description>Contact Open an issue on GitHub.
Email: rdligeralde@gmail.com
Phone: (513)-913-9266</description></item><item><title>Harmonizer, Explained</title><link>https://RDLigeralde.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/page/markdown-cheat-sheet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://RDLigeralde.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/page/markdown-cheat-sheet/</guid><description>One of the most common questions we receive at Muse is how exactly our Harmonizer service functions. While we don&amp;rsquo;t intend to give away all of our company secrets quite yet (¯\_(ツ)_/¯), in the interest of transparency we&amp;rsquo;ve decided to provide a brief overview of the approach our algorithm takes to find your future listening partners.
Step 1: Gathering User Data The first step involves collecting data on users&amp;rsquo; listening habits.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://RDLigeralde.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://RDLigeralde.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Privacy Policy TLDR: We do not use cookies and we do not collect any personal data.
Website visitors No personal information is collected. No information is stored in the browser. No information is shared with, sent to or sold to third-parties. No information is shared with advertising companies. No information is mined and harvested for personal and behavioral trends. No information is monetized. Information we collect and what we use it for The server hosting this site can collect the following information:</description></item><item><title>Sobre</title><link>https://RDLigeralde.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/about.pt/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://RDLigeralde.github.io/hugo-mock-landing-page-domain-name/about.pt/</guid><description>Sobre nós Feito com ❤️ pela equipa Hugo Bootstrap Theme.</description></item></channel></rss>